<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic-7076" xml:lang="en-us" class="- topic/topic "><title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 5</title><shortdesc class="- topic/shortdesc "/><prolog class="- topic/prolog "><author translate="no" type="creator" class="- topic/author ">Leah Van Blaricom &lt;leahvb@vt.edu&gt;</author><metadata class="- topic/metadata "><keywords class="- topic/keywords "/></metadata></prolog><body class="- topic/body "><p class="- topic/p ">The wolf noticed a chimney attached to the house. He decided to climb up the house, onto the roof, to enter the piggies house through the chimney. </p><p class="- topic/p ">However, the wolf did not know that the huge pot of stew on an open fire was right below the chimney. </p><p audience="children" class="- topic/p ">The wolf flew down the chimney and fell right into the pot of stew!!! <fig audience="children" class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">The wolf fell into the stew, and the piggies all laughed at him! </title><image alt="wolf in a huge pot of soup. photo is for children" href="wolfinstew.jpeg" class="- topic/image "/></fig></p><p audience="children" class="- topic/p ">The wolf decided to have a bite of the stew before he ate the piggies. He said, "This is the best meal I have ever had!"</p><p audience="children" class="- topic/p ">The third little piggie was thrilled. He said to the wolf, "You can have as much stew as you want, as long as you promise to never blow my siblings' houses down again and never try to eat them again!" </p><p audience="children" class="- topic/p ">The wolf proclaimed, "I promise!!" </p><p audience="children" class="- topic/p ">The three little piggies and the wolf ate the stew together, and became friends. They all lived happily ever after! </p><p audience="adult" class="- topic/p ">The wolf fell right into the huge, boiling stew that was extremely hot! The wolf died instantly. </p><p audience="adult" class="- topic/p ">The third piggie thought to himself, "Yum!! I know what I am eating tonight!"<fig audience="adult" class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">The wolf fell right into the boiling pot of stew! </title><image alt="wolf falling to his death into a big pot of stew. photo for adults." href="wolfinboil.jpeg" class="- topic/image "/></fig>The third little piggie ate the whole wolf up! He lived a very long and happy life. He lived happily ever after! </p><p class="- topic/p ">The End</p></body></topic>