<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "topic.dtd">
<topic id="topic-9763" xml:lang="en-us" class="- topic/topic "><title class="- topic/title ">Chapter 3</title><shortdesc class="- topic/shortdesc "/><prolog class="- topic/prolog "><author translate="no" type="creator" class="- topic/author ">Leah Van Blaricom &lt;leahvb@vt.edu&gt;</author><metadata class="- topic/metadata "><keywords class="- topic/keywords "/></metadata></prolog><body class="- topic/body "><p class="- topic/p ">The wolf, still hungry for little piggies, was prowling the forest for dinner and came across a stick house. He thought to himself, "Not as easy as straw... but I can blow that down!"<fig class="- topic/fig "><title class="- topic/title ">The wolf was getting more hungry and more angry! </title><image alt="photo of an angry wolf" href="angrywolf.jpeg" class="- topic/image "/></fig></p><p audience="children" class="- topic/p ">He looked inside the house and he saw two little piggies, he thought, "Yum! I know what I am having for dinner!" </p><p audience="adult" class="- topic/p ">He looked inside the house and saw another little piggie, he thought, "Yum! Porkchops for dinner!"</p><p class="- topic/p ">He knocked on the door and said: </p><p conref="reuse.dita#topic-4832/letmein" class="- topic/p "/><p audience="children" class="- topic/p ">The little pigs shook with fear. The first pig knew this was the wolf, and told his brother they could not open the door! They said: </p><p audience="adult" class="- topic/p ">The little pig shook with fear. He saw the wolf's teeth through the peephole in the door. He said: </p><p audience="children" conref="reuse.dita#topic-4832/ourchin" class="- topic/p "/><p audience="adult" conref="reuse.dita#topic-4832/mychinadult" class="- topic/p "/><p class="- topic/p ">The wolf grew angrier. He said:</p><p conref="reuse.dita#topic-4832/huffandpuff" class="- topic/p "/><p class="- topic/p ">The wolf huffed and puffed. The house did not come down on the first huff and puff. The piggies thought they were safe! But, the wolf mustered up his strength and huffed and puffed again! This time, the house blew down! </p><p class="- topic/p ">The wolf was fast... </p><p audience="children" class="- topic/p ">But not fast enough for the piggies! The piggies teamed up to make obstacles for the wolf. He tripped over chairs, tables, and other obstacles the piggies knocked over. The two piggies ran all the way to the third little piggies brick house. </p><p audience="adult" class="- topic/p ">Way too fast for the piggie. The wolf made himself comfortable in the ruins of the straw house, and had himself a yummy pork chop dinner. </p></body></topic>